(Leonard:)'cause a lot of people lose
their virginity on prom night.
(Sheldon:)Penny implied the same thing.
(Sheldon:)Is this true?
(Leonard:)Just relax, it's a joke.
(Leonard:)You don't have
hormones.
(Leonard:)Wow, you look amazing.
(Penny:)Thank you, so do you.
(Amy:)Sheldon,
you look so handsome.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Sheldon, doesn't Amy look hot?
(Penny:)That's got to put some starch
in the upper flermin.
(Amy:)What's that?
(Leonard:)Oh, it's a scaly
genital organ
(Leonard:)that grows between
his shoulder blades.
(Leonard:)Try not to touch it
when you're dancing.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Amy:)Where are you going?
(Sheldon:)I can't do this.
(Sheldon:)And for your information,
Leonard,
(Sheldon:)the upper flermin doesn't grow
between my shoulder blades,
(Sheldon:)it grows out of the belly button
on my neck.